<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>The compulsive list maker</title>
  
  <link href="/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  
  <link href="http://thecompulsivelistmaker.com/"/>
  <updated>2017-07-01T22:57:47.000Z</updated>
  <id>http://thecompulsivelistmaker.com/</id>
  
  <author>
    <name>list maker</name>
    
  </author>
  
  <generator uri="http://hexo.io/">Hexo</generator>
  
  <entry>
    <title>The Crate</title>
    <link href="http://thecompulsivelistmaker.com/pet/the-crate/"/>
    <id>http://thecompulsivelistmaker.com/pet/the-crate/</id>
    <published>2017-07-01T18:00:07.000Z</published>
    <updated>2017-07-01T22:57:47.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The crate I went with was the <a href="https://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B0002AT3ME" target="_blank" rel="external">MidWest Life Stages Folding Metal Dog Crate</a>. The 42-inch should work for my golden retriever puppy now and when he grows up with the bult in divider since the crate should be just large enough for the pup to stand up and turn around in. There is a size chart on the product for most popular breed’s adult size or you can approximate to one of the breeds listed there.</p>
<p>I had also started feeding my puppy exclusively in the crate as the bottom can be removed and wiped off easily if he made a mess. This also had the unintended effect of him actually associating crate with food and actually likes the crate.</p>
<p>I do think the single door version might have been good enough for me.</p>
<p>Overall it feels sturdy and looks and feels well constructed.</p>
<p>I also ended up buying the matching 42-inch <a href="https://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B003D7LCQS" target="_blank" rel="external">MidWest Polyester Crate Cover for Wire Crates</a>, but if you don’t want to spend the extra $X you can make do with a blanket. I don’t regret my purchase since the fit is precise and looks nice. This was primarily supposed to create that “den-like” feeling for the pup which it might or might not have, but the bigger win for me is it blocks out light and lets him sleep longer into the mornings. It also seems to help him with his afternoon naps since my pup seems to gets really active when the sun is out.</p>
]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;The crate I went with was the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B0002AT3ME&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;external&quot;&gt;MidWest Life Stages F
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="pet" scheme="http://thecompulsivelistmaker.com/categories/pet/"/>
    
    
      <category term="pet" scheme="http://thecompulsivelistmaker.com/tags/pet/"/>
    
      <category term="training" scheme="http://thecompulsivelistmaker.com/tags/training/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
</feed>
